During a Sunday Service at The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophetic message
in which he referred to February as being a peculiar month in the Southern African subregion.
These were his words...
Ending of February - very peculiar month in the Southern African subregion.
I will not say more than that.
It means they have to be steadfast in prayer.
Ending of February is a peculiar month in the Southern African subregion.
Let us observe prayer sessions in the beginning for the leaders.
Ending of February to April.
That is, from the ending of February to April.
Let us observe prayer sessions.
I will let you know of further messages as they are revealed to me.